<resources>
    <string name="app_name">RxStarter</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_single">SingleActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_button_click">ButtonClickActivity</string>
    <string name="explanation_button_click">The .throttleFirst() function filters out any clicks that comes out faster than once per second.   The .scan() function keeps a running tally of all emissions that make it past the filter.</string>
    <string name="explanation_thread_switch">The No Threading button keeps everything on the same thread, which locks things up if the process takes long.   The good threading button uses \'observeOn(Schedulers.computation())\' to put the long-running process on a separate thread, and \'observeOn(AndroidSchedulers.mainThread())\' to put it back on the ui thread.</string>
    <string name="explanation_failing_api">The ".doOnRetry()" function updates the textview every time there\'s a timeout error. \n\n The ".retryWhen()" function restarts the api call if there is a timeoutError.</string>
    <string name="explanation_long_load">One Rx Stream does a long api call that takes 4–40 seconds.\n\nThe other stream emits a random number every 3 seconds and sets a loading text based on that.</string>
    <string name="explanation_distinct">Every 200ms, a new random value is emitted, but only values which have not been emitted before get past the filter to the textView. \n\nValues are still being emitted silently right now but get filtered out by distinct()</string>
    <string name="explanation_pin">The .mergeWith() function merges all button clicks into a single stream. \n\n.buffer(4) prevents stream emissions until 4 numbers are entered. \n\n.doOnNext() causes a vibration if any button is clicked</string>
    <string name="explanation_list">A single PublishSubject(String) emits a String every 100ms. \n\n The Observer which listens to this Publisher is passed to the ListAdapter, which sets a listener on each list item. </string>

    <string-array name="loading_messages">
        <item>Loading…</item>
        <item>We\'re working on it…</item>
        <item>Things are happening…</item>
        <item>Reticulating splines…</item>
        <item>Making the universe…</item>
        <item>Baking an Android Pie…</item>
        <item>Mutating from a single-celled app…</item>
        <item>Reacting to Co-routines…</item>
        <item>Observing the observer…</item>
        <item>Emitting a stream…</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
